A Guide to the Papers of Howard W. Smith, 1933-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Miscellaneous Legislation
  - Immigration Legislation - 89th Congress (Box 94)
  - Interest Rate Bill (Box 94)
  - Labor - Wage-Hour Minimum Wage - 89th Congress (Box 94)
  - Labor - Legislation-89th Congress (Box 95)
  - District of Columbia-89th Congress (Box 95)
  - D.C. Committee (Box 96)
  - Home Rule - D.C. [89th Congress] 1st Session (Box 96)
  - Pending Bills - D.C. Committee (Box 97)
  - Transportation - D.C. (Rapid Transit Compact) (Box 97)
  - Rapid Transportation Compact (Box 97)
  - Education Legislation -89th Congress (Box 98)
  - Appropriations - 89th Congress (Box 99)
  - Appalachian Regional Development Act of 1965 (Box 99)
  - Mt. Vernon-Appropriation (Box 99)
  - Banking Legislation (Balance of Payments) (Box 100)
  - Bank Holding Act - Financial (Box 100)
  - Banking - Balance of payments - 89th Congress (Box 100)
  - Civil Rights Bill of 1966 - 89th Congress, 2nd Session (Box 100)
  - Civil Rights Legislation (Box 101)
  - Civil Service (Box 101)
  - H.R. 3-to establish rules of interpretation governing questions of the effect of Acts of Congress on state laws (Box 101)
  - H.R. 3-to establish rules of interpretation governing questions of the effect of Acts of Congress on state laws (Box 102-105)
  - H.R. 6127-to establish a Civil Rights Commission - 85th Congress (Box 106)
  - Follow-up correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 106)
  - Segregation Records - consisting mainly of letters, reports and clippings on the Segregation issue in Virginia, 1956-1960 (Box 106)
  - Civil Rights-85th Congress (Box 106)
  - Civil Rights-Point of Order - Ramseyer Bill (Box 107)
  - Civil Rights Legislation (Box 107)
  - Journal - Civil Rights (Box 107)
  - Civil rights - [Correspondence] (Box 107)
  - Civil rights - [Correspondence] (Box 108)
  - Letter to the President on Civil Rights (Box 108)
  - Segregation-85th Congress (Box 108)
  - Litigation, 1958 Session of Schools (Box 108)
  - Segregation-Acts of Legislature relating to Segregation, etc. (Box 109)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, 4th Circuit - No. 7430, School Board of City of Newport News vs. Jerome A. Atkins (Box 109)
  - "Five Years of Progress, 1953-1958" (Report of the President's Committee on Government Contracts) (Box 109)
  - Segregation - Little rock (Box 109)
  - School Segregation Question in Virginia - January, 1960 (Box 109)
  - Segregation File #4 (Box 109)
  - Segregation of Races in Public Schools (Box 109)
  - Legislation [Segregation] - Documents used in connection with conference with Governor Stanley (Box 110)
  - Segregation (Box 110)
    3 folders
  - Segregation Legislation (Box 111)
  - Segregation (Box 111)
  - Coal - 89th Congress (Box 111)
- Series III. Miscellaneous Correspondence
  - 84th Congress, Correspondence
    - Misc. Correspondence "A" (Box 112)
    - Appointments for Personal Conferences (Box 112)
    - Requests for U.S. Department of Agriculture Yearbook (Box 112)
      2 folders
    - Army-Navy Game, 1955 & 1956 (Box 112)
    - Anderson Orthopedia Hospital (Alexandria, Va.) (Box 112)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (proposed building in Virginia) (Box 112)
    - Congressional Record, Feb. 7, 1964 (Box 112)
    - Misc. Correspondence "B" (Box 113)
    - re: Bridges & tunnels across the Potomac, correspondence and bills, 1939-1956 (Box 113)
    - Misc. Correspondence "C" (Box 113)
    - Congressional Secretaries Club (Box 114)
    - Census, 1954-1955 (Box 114)
    - Central Intelligience Agency Office Building (Box 114)
    - Charlottesville Airport (Box 114)
    - Government Geogrpahical and Navigation Charts (2 folders) (Box 114)
    - Personal contributions (Box 114)
    - The Commonwealth (article re: Judge Smith) (Box 114)
    - Misc. Correspondence "D" (Box 115)
    - Democratic National Congressional Committee and Democratic National Committee - 83rd Congress (Box 115)
    - Drought Relief Program (Box 115)
    - Misc. Correspondence "E" (Box 115)
    - Messages of President Eisenhower (Box 115)
    - Mis. Correspondence "F" (Box 116)
    - Forms - Civil Service, V.A., etc. (Box 116)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service - Dept. of Interior (2 folders) (Box 116)
    - Farmers' Bulletins (Box 116)
    - Misc. Correspondence "O" (Box 116)
    - Orchard Grass - market threatened (Box 116)
    - Misc. Correspondence "P" (Box 117)
    - Patronage (Box 117)
    - Misc. Correspondence "Q" (Box 117)
    - Misc. Correspondence "R" (Box 117)
    - REA and Va. Elec. Corp. (Box 117)
    - Requests for Information, etc. (2 folders) (Box 117)
    - Misc. Correspondence "S" (Box 118)
    - Soy Beans (Box 118)
    - For Relief of Thomas J. Smith (Box 118)
    - Schools (miscellaneous) (Box 118)
    - High Schools in 8th District (Box 118)
    - Misc. speeches by Judge Smith (Box 118)
    - Misc. Correspondence "T" (Box 119)
    - Telephone & Telegram Association - bills, receipts, etc. (Box 119)
    - Misc. Correspondence "U" (Box 119)
    - Misc. Correspondence "V" (Box 119)
    - Va. Elections and Power Correspondence (Box 119)
    - Va. Legislature (Box 119)
    - Misc. Correspondence "W" (Box 119)
    - White House tours (Box 119)
    - Western Union messages (Box 119)
    - Misc. Correspondence "X, Y, Z" (Box 119)
    - Yorktown Monument (Box 119)
  - 85th Congress - Correspondence (Box 120)
    - Misc. Correspondence "A" (Box 120)
    - Armories (Box 120)
    - Army-Navy game, 1957-1958 (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - American Good Government Society Award (Box 120)
    - Attorney General Election (Va., 1957) (Box 120)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Sale - Military Installations (Box 120)
    - Airports (Box 120)
    - Department of Agriculture Yearbooks requests (Box 120)
    - Balls Bluff Cemetery (Civil War Monument) (Box 121)
    - Bridges and Tunnels (Box 121)
    - Misc. Correspondence "B" (Box 121)
    - Misc. Correspondence "C" (Box 121)
    - Charts - geographical and navigational (Box 122)
    - Congressional Record - references to (Box 122)
    - Congressional Directory - requests for (Box 122)
    - Clippings (newspaper) (Box 122)
    - Congressional Secretaries Club (Box 122)
    - Personal contributions (Box 122)
    - Misc. Correspondence "D" (Box 123)
    - District Engineer - matters in 8th District re: rivers, harbors, etc. (Box 123)
    - Misc. Correspondence "E" (Box 123)
    - Pres. Eisenhower Messages - 85th Congress (Box 123)
    - Misc. Correspondence "F" (Box 124)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (Box 124)
    - Farmers' Bulletins (Box 124)
    - Misc. Correspondence "G" (Box 124)
    - Gallery passes (requests) (Box 124)
    - Government information - 85th Congress (Box 124)
    - Gubernatorial Election, Va. - 1957 (Box 124)
    - Misc. Correspondence "H" (Box 125)
    - Highways - Va. (Box 125)
    - Appointments to Va. Highway Commission, 1957 (Box 125)
    - Misc. Correspondence "I" (Box 125)
    - Invitations Declined (2 folders) (Box 125)
    - Invitations Accepted (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - Inaugurations (1957) (Box 126)
    - Misc. Correspondence "J" (Box 126)
    - Jamestown Festival (Box 126)
    - Misc. Correspondence "K" (Box 126)
    - Misc. Correspondence "L" (Box 126)
    - Misc. Correspondence "M" (Box 126)
    - Library of Congress (Box 127)
    - Liaison Officers (Box 127)
    - John Marshall Centennial (Box 127)
    - Md. -Va. Milk Producers Association - printed matter (Box 127)
    - Md. -Va. Milk Producers Association Anti - Trust Suit (Box 127)
    - Misc. Correspondence "O" (Box 128)
    - National Monument Commission (Box 128)
    - Office File (Box 128)
    - Misc. Correspondence "P" (Box 128)
    - Press Releases (Box 128)
    - Potomac River Oyster Commission (Box 128)
    - Misc. Correspondence "Q" (Box 128)
    - Misc. Correspondence "R" (Box 129)
    - Roads (Box 129)
    - Requests for Information, etc. (Box 129)
    - Misc. Correspondence "S" (Box 130)
    - Stationery - receipts, etc. (Box 130)
    - Speeches by Judge Smith (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - Schools (Box 131)
    - Speeches by Judge Smith (2 folders) (Box 131)
    - Misc. Correspondence "T" (Box 131)
    - Telephone & Telegram accounts (Box 131)
    - Misc. Correspondence "U" (Box 131)
    - Misc. Correspondence "V" (Box 131)
    - Va. Delegation in Congress (Box 131)
    - Misc. Correspondence "W" (Box 132)
    - Misc. Correspondence "X,Y,Z" (Box 132)
    - President's Advisory Committee on Presidential Office Space (Box 132)
    - Misc. Correspondence "A" (Box 133)
    - Agricultural Yearbook request (Box 133)
    - Army-Navy game requests (Box 133)
    - Appointments (Box 133)
    - Misc. Correspondence "B" (Box 133)
  - 86th Congress - Correspondence
    - Misc. Correspondence "C" (Box 134)
    - Capitol Calendars - 83rd-86th Congress (Box 134)
    - Chantilly Airport, sewage, road, etc. - (3 folders) (Box 134)
    - Complimentary Letters - 85th Congress, 2nd Session (Box 135)
    - Congressional Directory (Box 135)
    - Congressional Record (Box 135)
    - Congressional Secretaries Club (Box 135)
    - Contributions (Box 135)
    - Charts (Box 135)
    - Democratic National Committee (Box 135)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1960 (Box 135)
    - Dahlgren Land Acquisitions (Box 135)
    - District Engineer - re: matters in 8th District (Box 135)
    - Misc. Correspondence "E" (Box 136)
    - Misc. Correspondence "F" (Box 136)
    - Farmers' Bulletins (Box 136)
    - Misc. Correspondence "G" (Box 136)
    - Gallery requests (Box 136)
    - Government information (Box 136)
    - Misc. Correspondence "D" (Box 137)
    - Misc. Correspondence "H" (Box 137)
    - Health, Education & Welfare (Box 137)
    - Misc. Correspondence "I" (Box 137)
    - Farm Bureau Dinner, Oct. 29, 1960 (Box 138)
    - Invitations Accepted (Box 138)
    - Invitations Declined (Box 138)
    - Misc. Correspondence "J" (Box 138)
    - Misc. Correspondence "K" (Box 138)
    - Misc. Correspondence "L" (Box 139)
    - "Liaison" Office (Box 139)
    - Library of Congress (Box 139)
    - Moc Lerner of H. Olsher re: D.C. Transit (Box 139)
    - Misc. Correspondence "M" (Box 139)
    - Md.-Va. Milk Producers Association, 1959 (2 folders) (Box 140)
    - Misc. Correspondence "N" (Box 140)
    - Misc. Correspondence "O" (Box 140)
    - Organization of 86th Congress (Box 141)
    - Office File (Box 141)
    - John Lee Pratt re: VA. Boundary lines (Box 141)
    - Potomac River Dam (Box 141)
    - Misc. Correspondence "P" (Box 141)
    - Misc. Correspondence "Q" (Box 141)
    - Quantico-Wage Scale (Box 141)
    - Misc. Correspondence "R" (Box 141)
    - Roads (Box 142)
    - Misc. Correspondence "S" (Box 142)
    - Soil Survey (Box 142)
    - Stationery Room - Receipts, bills, etc. (Box 142)
    - Requests (Box 143)
    - Misc. Correspondence "T" (Box 143)
    - Telephone & Telegraph Accounts (Box 143)
    - Misc. Correspondence "U" (Box 143)
    - Misc. Correspondence "V" (Box 143)
    - Misc. Correspondence "W" (Box 143)
    - Va. Congressional Delegation (Box 144)
    - Wage Rate (Vint Hill, etc.) (Box 144)
    - White House (Box 144)
    - Wall Street Journal article on Judge Smith (Box 144)
    - Misc. Correspondence "X,Y,Z" (Box 144)
  - 87th Congress - Correspondence
    - Misc. Correspondence "A" (Box 145)
    - Agricultural Yearbooks (Box 145)
    - Appointments (Box 145)
    - Lindsay Almond re: integration (Box 145)
    - Misc. Correspondence "B" (Box 146)
    - Bolling Air Force Base: Open Mess (Box 146)
    - Judge John D. Butzner re: federal judgeship (Box 146)
    - Misc. Correspondence "C" (Box 147)
    - Chantilly Airport (Box 147)
    - Charts (Box 147)
    - Contributors (Box 147)
    - Congressional Record (Box 147)
    - Calendar requests (Box 148)
    - Complimentary Letters (Box 148)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 148)
    - Va. State Chamber of Commerce Award to Judge Smith (Box 148)
    - Compacts: Potomac River (Box 148)
    - Civil Works Program Budget (Box 148)
    - Misc. Correspondence "D" (Box 148)
    - District Engineer (Box 148)
    - Misc. Correspondence "E" (Box 149)
    - Dr. Morris Eigen re: Smith sale of cattle (Box 149)
    - Misc. Correspondence "F" (Box 149)
    - Fredeuchisbaig Airline Service (Box 149)
    - Farmer's Bulletins (Box 149)
    - James Flanagan re: prejudice (Box 149)
    - Misc. Correspondence "G" (Box 149)
    - Government information (Box 149)
    - Gallery requests (Box 149)
    - Misc. Correspondence "H" (Box 150)
    - Calvin Haley - Judge Smith's Secretary (personal correspondence of) (Box 150)
    - Misc. Correspondence "I" (Box 150)
    - Invitations accepted (Box 150)
    - Invitations declined (Box 151)
    - Misc. Correspondence "J" (Box 151)
    - Misc. Correspondence "K" (Box 152)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Dinner, Feb. 17, 1962 (Box 152)
    - Kennedy Administration Appointments (Box 152)
    - Misc. Correspondence "L" (Box 152)
    - List - re: address of Lobbyists (?) (Box 152)
    - Contributions (Box 152)
    - Misc. Correspondence "M" (Box 152)
    - Mississippi: article- Congressional Record (Box 153)
    - Monroe Doctrine: Library of Congress reference (Box 153)
    - U.S. Marshalls (Box 153)
    - First Manassas Corp. (Box 153)
    - Md.-Va. Milk Producers Association (Box 153)
    - Mean File - adverse comments on Judge Smith (Box 153)
    - Newspaper and Radio Stations (Box 153)
    - Misc. Correspondence "N" (Box 153)
    - Misc. Correspondence "O" (Box 153)
    - Office matters (Box 154)
    - Misc. Correspondence "P" (Box 154)
    - Misc. Correspondence "Q" (Box 154)
    - Misc. Correspondence "R" (Box 154)
    - Requests (Box 155)
    - Roads (Box 155)
    - Misc. Correspondence "S" (Box 155)
    - Smoot Sand and Gravel (Box 156)
    - Silk: V.R. Shackelford, Jr. (Box 156)
    - Cong. Howard W. Smith: Soil conservation (Box 156)
    - Supreme Court Decisions (Box 156)
    - Stationery room - bills, etc. (Box 156)
    - Misc. Correspondence "T" (Box 157)
    - Telephone, etc., bills, etc. (Box 157)
    - Misc. Correspondence "U" (Box 157)
    - Misc. Correspondence "V" (Box 157)
    - Va. District Y.M.C.A. (Box 157)
    - Misc. Correspondence "W" (Box 157)
    - Misc. Correspondence "X" (Box 157)
    - Misc. Correspondence "Y" (Box 157)
    - Misc. Correspondence "Z" (Box 157)
  - 88th Congress - Correspondence
    - Misc. Correspondence "A" (Box 158)
    - Appointments (Box 158)
    - Army-Navy Game (87th Congress) (Box 158)
    - Agricultural Yearbooks - requests (Box 158)
    - Misc. Correspondence "B" (Box 159)
    - Misc. Correspondence "C" (Box 160)
    - Charts (Box 160)
    - Congressional Record (Box 160)
    - Water Research Lab (Charlottesville) (Box 160)
    - Calendars (Box 160)
    - Complimentary Letters (Box 160)
    - Dulles Airport (Box 161)
    - Misc. Correspondence "E" (Box 161)
    - Erosion (Box 161)
    - Misc. Correspondence "F" (Box 161)
    - Farmers' Bulletin requests (Box 161)
    - Emergency Feed Grain Program (Box 161)
    - Misc. Correspondence "G" (Box 162)
    - Gallery (Box 162)
    - Misc. Correspondence "H" (Box 162)
    - H.E.W. and other grants (Box 163)
    - Misc. Correspondence "I" (Box 163)
    - Invitations Accepted (Box 163)
    - Invitations Declined (Box 163)
    - Industrial Development in Virginia (Box 164)
    - Invitations Accepted (Box 164)
    - Invitations Declined (Box 164)
    - Inaugural, 1965 (Box 164)
    - Misc. Correspondence "J" (Box 165)
    - Misc. Correspondence "k" (Box 165)
    - Kennedy - Assassination (Box 165)
    - Misc. Correspondence "L" (Box 165)
    - Library of Congress - 87th Congress (Box 165)
    - Misc. Correspondence "M" (Box 166)
    - Md.-Va. Milk Producers Association (Box 166)
    - Misc. Correspondence "N" (Box 166)
    - Misc. Correspondence "O" (Box 166)
    - Office Correspondence (Box 167)
    - Misc. Correspondence "P" (Box 167)
    - Prayer Decision - Su-preme Court (Box 167)
    - Misc. Correspondence "Q" (Box 168)
    - Misc. Correspondence "R" (Box 168)
    - Roads (Box 168)
    - Misc. Correspondence "S" (Box 168)
    - Stationery, receipts, etc. (Box 169)
    - Misc. Correspondence "T" (Box 169)
    - Telephone & Telegraph, etc. (Box 169)
    - Misc. Correspondence "V" (Box 169)
    - Misc. Correspondence "W" (Box 169)
    - White House: President's Messages (Box 170)
    - Misc. Correspondence "U" (Box 170)
    - Executive Orders: Authority of President (Box 170)
    - Misc. Correspondence "X,Y,Z" (Box 170)
  - 86th, 87th, 88th Congress - Correspondence
    - Public Works Commission: Tabbs Creek, Va. (Box 171)
    - Potomac River Basin (Box 171)
    - Drought Relief Program (Box 171)
    - Dahlgren - 87th Congress (Box 171)
    - Misc. Correspondence "D" - 88th Congress (Box 171)
    - D.C. Engineers - 88th Congress (Box 172)
    - Misc. Corrrespondence "E" - 88th Congress (Box 172)
    - Misc. Corrrespondence "F" - 87th-88th Congress (Box 172)
    - Fish and Wildlife Commission - 87th Congress (Box 172)
    - Howard Friend - Interior Department and Appropriations (Box 172)
    - Misc. Correspondence "G" (Box 173)
    - Gallery - 88th Congress (Box 173)
    - Forms, etc. - 86th Congress (Box 173)
    - Misc. Correspondence "H" - 87th-88th Congress (Box 173)
    - Health, Education & Welfare - 87th Congress (Box 174)
    - Mr. Haley - 88th Congress (Box 174)
  - 89th Congress - Correspondence
    - Misc. Correspondence "A" (Box 175)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 175)
    - Annual Report of Caroline County A.S.C.S. (Box 175)
    - Army Liaison (Box 175)
    - Airport (Box 175)
    - Appointments (Box 175)
    - Agricultural Yearbook (Box 175)
    - Army-Navy tickets (Box 175)
    - Misc. Correspondence "B" (Box 176)
    - Misc. Correspondence "C" (Box 176)
    - Congressional Directory - 87th Congress (Box 176)
    - Congressional Record (Box 176)
    - Census (Box 176)
    - Charts (Box 176)
    - Civil Rights Debate, 1966 - Speech (Box 177)
    - Misc. Correspondence "D" (Box 177)
    - District Engineers (Box 177)
    - H.R. 4430 - improvement of Hull Creek, Va. - 85th Congress (Box 177)
    - Bonum Creek, Virginia (Box 177)
    - Invitations Declined (Box 178)
    - Misc. Correspondence "J" (Box 178)
    - Misc. Correspondence "K" (Box 178)
    - Misc. Correspondence "L" (Box 179)
    - Lorton, (Va.) Reformatory (Box 179)
    - Library of Congress (Box 179)
    - Misc. Correspondence "M" (Box 180)
    - Misc. Correspondence "N" (Box 180)
    - Thomas Nelson Jr. Award (Box 180)
    - Misc. Correspondence "O" (Box 180)
    - Office (2 folders) (Box 181)
    - O.E.O. Programs - 8th District (Box 182)
    - Misc. Correspondence "P" (Box 182)
    - State Parks (Box 182)
    - Potomac River - Recreation Sites (Box 182)
    - Stafford Co. Water Reservoir Project: Quantico Marine Base Land (Box 182)
    - Water Pollution: Prince William (Box 182)
    - Prince William: Acquire Manassas Air Force Station for training center (Box 182)
    - Loudon County Dam (Box 182)
    - Sewage and Water Grants (Box 182)
    - Potomac Watershed - Stafford County (Box 183)
    - Prayer Decision (Box 183)
    - Presidential Messages (Box 183)
    - Misc. Correspondence "Q" (Box 183)
    - Misc. Correspondence "R" (Box 183)
    - Randolph Macon College (Box 183)
    - Roads (Box 183)
    - Requests (3 folders) (Box 184)
    - Reapportionment - Virginia (Box 185)
    - Misc. Correspondence "S" (Box 185)
    - Louisa South Anna Watershed Plan (Box 186)
    - Soil Survey - 87th Congress (Box 186)
    - Small Business Administration (Box 186)
    - Stationery Account (Box 186)
    - Misc. Correspondence "T" (Box 186)
    - Telephone & Telepgraph (Box 186)
    - Misc. Correspondence "U" (Box 186)
    - Misc. Correspondence "V" (Box 186)
    - Misc. Correspondence "W" (Box 187)
    - Washington & Old Dominon Railroad (Box 187)
    - Misc. Correspondence "X,Y,Z" (Box 187)
- Series IV. Private Bills
  - Bills for Relief of ... (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2935 - Roger Sanford, introduced Feb. 24, 1949 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2935-Mrs. Benjamin Betts, introduced Feb. 21, 1949 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 3732-Robert I. Cryster, introduced March 22, 1949 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 4108-Ladislas E. Hudec, introduced April 7, 1949 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 4109-Kenneth McKelvie, introduced April 7, 1949 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 8563-Alonzo P. Brown, May 18, 1950 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 1930-Vincenzo Carannante, Jan. 22, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 1931-Orange henrique Gomes, Jan. 22, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2310-Jindrich and Zdenka Nosek, Jan. 31, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2413-Kloman Instrument Co. Inc., Feb. 5, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2415-Maurice Mumford, Feb. 5, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2414-Arthur C. Thompson, Feb. 5, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2549-Talmage Wilcher, Inc., Feb. 8, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2550-Thomas C. Digges, Feb. 8, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2251-Mt. Vernon Chapter, D.A.R., Feb. 8, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2920-priscilla Ogden Dickerson, etc., Feb. 26, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 3187 - Cornelia Mayr, March 12, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 4762-Deborah A. Hudson, July 10, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 5541-Capt. Walter C. Wolf, Sept. 27, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 5759-Chizuko Nakagami, Oct. 16, 1951 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 8872-Michael A. Gardiner, Jan. 26, 1956 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 2436Avesti V. Baicousheff, re-introduced Jan. 29, 1953 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 1966-Dezso Szilagyi, Jan. 5, 1956 (Box 188)
    - H.R. 8087-Paul G. Abernathy, Jan. 3, 1956 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 9947-William Ed Wine, March 13, 1956 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 11618-Katherine F. Colbert & Choldren, June 5, 1956 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 12165-Dionesios Silverthes, July 9, 1956 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 12295-Mrs. Ruth Edwards, Barry, July 17, 1956 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 3396-Dr. Hamdi Akar, Feb. 23, 1953 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 5094-Thomas J. Smith, May 7, 1953 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 5822-Evanthia Demetios, June 17, 1953 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 4196-Mary Goodyear Brown, March 23, 1953 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 2814Funghin Liu Wang, Feb. 6, 1953 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 103-Ida Seringer Sanford, widow, Jan. 19, 1953 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 405-Sarah A. Mitchell, Jan. 14, 1954 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 703-Mary B. Holmes, Aug. 10, 1954 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 4875-John Henry Wright, Jr., Feb. 14, 1957 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 9607-Charles J. Campbell, Jan. 10, 1962 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 11125-Mrs. Blanche M. Napier, April 4, 1962 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 7115-Inga Maja Olsson, May 12, 1959 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 7661-Dolores Cocke Moyano, July 7, 1956 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 9516 -Hertha Zimmerman Gray (Box 189)
    - H.R. 13031-Angelos I. Maroulis, June 18, 1958 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 2804-Mrs. Jay McLean, Jan. 24, 1963 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 11224-5-Robert W. Talbot, May 12, 1964 (Box 189)
    - H.R. 1881-Martino I. Romero (Box 189)
    - H.R. 17137-Robert L. St. Martin (Box 189)
    - H.R. 10407-Keith Hills (Box 189)
- Series V: Speeches, Articles, Recordings, etc.
  - Consultative Assembly of the Council of Europe (Box 190)
  - Europe - Article on Council of Europe (Box 190)
  - Speech - Radio, 4/11/42 (Response to ) ["A National Labor Policy"] (Box 190)
  - Curbing Strikes in Defense Industries - speech, November 17, 1941 (Box 190)
  - Anti-Strike Bill - H.R. 4139 - Debate and Vote, December 3, 1941 (Box 190)
  - Article - December, 1944 - Virginia Law Review, relates to files on "Committee to Investigate Executive Agencies" (Box 190)
  - National Radio Forum, 4/20/42 (Box 190)
  - Speech - June 26, 1939, "The Milk Bill" (Box 190)
  - Congressional Record, June 7, 1940 (Box 190)
  - Town Hall of the Air - New York, November 27, 1941 - Defense Strikes" (Box 190)
  - Speech - Chicago, May 9, 1941 - National Metal Trades Association "Labor and Government" (Box 190)
  - Smith Amendments to N.L.R.B. Debate and Final Vote on -June 7, 1940 (Box 190)
  - 76th Congress
    - Alien Registration - debate and vote, July 29, 1939 (Box 191)